{
    "subject": "resource/11:14",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Henry_Thomas",
    "human_readable": "Henry Thomas stars in the movie 11:14.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9567583799362183,
            "question": "Has Henry Thomas starred in other movies besides 11:14?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8199983835220337,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie starring Henry Thomas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7996712327003479,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 11:14?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6761888861656189,
            "question": "Name a movie that features Henry Thomas."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6396737098693848,
            "question": "Is Henry Thomas an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6187578439712524,
            "question": "What are some other popular films starring Henry Thomas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3749373257160187,
            "question": "When was the movie 11:14 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2741369307041168,
            "question": "What genre is the movie 11:14 likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26062148809432983,
            "question": "Where can I watch the movie 11:14?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20870347321033478,
            "question": "Does the movie 11:14 have any sequels or prequels?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henry Thomas stars in the movie 11:14.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1678_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch the movie 11:14?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1678_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie 11:14 likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1678_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the movie 11:14 released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1678_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1678_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the documents mention Henry Thomas appearing in movies such as Cloak & Dagger (1984), Fire in the Sky (1993), Legends of the Fall (1994), Suicide Kings (1997), All the Pretty Horses (2000), Gangs of New York (2002), 11:14 (2003), and Dear John (2010). This information supports the triple that Henry Thomas stars in the movie 11:14."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indeed mention that Henry Thomas appeared in the film \"11:14 (2003)\". Therefore, the statement \"Henry Thomas stars in the movie 11:14\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}